# **Tyler Young**

## **Support Communicator and Documentation Writer**

Website: tyler-young.com Email: tyler@tyler-young.com Phone: (360) 601-4398 Location: Los Angeles, CA

Customer support expert with 4 years of experience in crafting user-friendly technical instructions for all skill levels. My goal is to be in a technical writing role as part of a team focused on customer success.

## **Experience**

### **Independent Developer**

May 2013 – Present

- Developed launch and marketing plan for independent iOS game (to be launched).
- Created a profitable algorithm for trading currencies on the foreign exchange market.
- Scripted in C#, JavaScript, and Python programming languages.

## **Customer Support Agent**

January 2014 – July 2017

Media Temple

- Troubleshot issues with LAMP servers, databases, website development, email.
- Maintained and updated knowledge base documentation.
- Wrote widely-adopted instructions and scripts for many common customer problems.
- Resolved customer tickets with a customer satisfaction rating of over 95%.
- Trained new team members, assisted other agents with troubleshooting.
- Member of incident management team for outages and customer-facing issues.

#### **Research Assistant**

May 2012 - May 2013

Willamette University

- Conducted studies using student and community-member participants.
- Co-authored published research paper and performed statistical analysis of results.

## **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Arts, Psychology**

June 2013

Willamette University College

- Merit Scholarship
- Thesis: The Effectiveness of Educational Video Games in a Classroom Setting

## **Achievements**

### Published research paper

August 2013

Dixon, K., Young, T. & Miller, J. (2013, August). The Influence of Selective Attention during Memory Retrieval on Subsequent Memory Performance in Young and Older Adults. Poster session presented at the 35th Annual Conference of the Cognitive Science Society. Berlin, Germany.

Eagle Scout May 2008

## Skills

Technical writing, JIRA, C#, JavaScript, Python, Linux, HTML, CSS, SQL, Git, Adobe Creative Suite, Graphic Design, Photography